var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَإِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "and Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِيهِ",
        "answer": "He gives",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "yu'tīhi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "He has given you",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "ātākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We gave him",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "waātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "So We gave",
        "pcklId": "509",
        "tlit": "faātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will give you",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "yu'tikum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِيهِ",
        "answer": "He gives it",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "yu'tīhi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آثَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their footsteps",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "āthārihim",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their reward",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ajruhum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their reward",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "ajrahum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَ",
        "answer": "He has taken",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "akhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْخَذُ",
        "answer": "will be accepted",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "yu'khadhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرُ",
        "answer": "and the Last",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhiru",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "416",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "418",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "(to) the earth",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْسَوْا",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tasaw",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "522",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "523",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "only",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1282",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those",
        "pcklId": "1283",
        "tlit": "fa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1284",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1285",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "1286",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "1287",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1288",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "1289",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "like those who",
        "pcklId": "1290",
        "tlit": "ka-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1291",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "But those who",
        "pcklId": "1292",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "1293",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1294",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "1295",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1296",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "1297",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "[to] Allah",
        "pcklId": "2565",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2566",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2567",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2568",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2569",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2570",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2571",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "while for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2572",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised",
        "pcklId": "2573",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2574",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2575",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2576",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "about Allah",
        "pcklId": "2577",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "at (the) remembrance (of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2578",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2579",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2580",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2581",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2582",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2583",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2584",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2585",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2586",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2587",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2588",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and so that Allah may make evident",
        "pcklId": "2589",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2590",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2591",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2592",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2593",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2594",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is) in Allah s Hand",
        "pcklId": "2595",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2596",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "and to",
        "pcklId": "666",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "into",
        "pcklId": "667",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "668",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمَدُ",
        "answer": "the term",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-amadu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَأْمُرُونَ",
        "answer": "and enjoin",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wayamurūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمُورُ",
        "answer": "the matters",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-umūru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرُ",
        "answer": "(the) Command",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "amru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنُوا",
        "answer": "Believe",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "āminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "you believe",
        "pcklId": "494",
        "tlit": "tu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "that you believe",
        "pcklId": "495",
        "tlit": "litu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "496",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "500",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "O you who believe",
        "pcklId": "501",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمِنُوا",
        "answer": "and believe",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "waāminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "829",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believing men",
        "pcklId": "830",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the believing women",
        "pcklId": "863",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'mināti",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْنِ",
        "answer": "come (the) time",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yani",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلُ",
        "answer": "(the) People",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "ahlu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلُ",
        "answer": "(is) the First",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-awalu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَأْوَاكُمُ",
        "answer": "Your abode",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "mawākumu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "Verses",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "āyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "and wretched is",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسٌ",
        "answer": "(is) power",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "basun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْخَلُونَ",
        "answer": "are stingy",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yabkhalūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبُخْلِ",
        "answer": "stinginess",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bil-bukh'li",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتَدَعُوهَا",
        "answer": "they innovated ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ib'tadaʿūhā",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبْرَأَهَا",
        "answer": "We bring it into existence",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nabra-ahā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُشْرَاكُمُ",
        "answer": "Glad tidings for you",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "bush'rākumu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-seer",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَاطِنُ",
        "answer": "and the Unapparent",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wal-bāṭinu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاطِنُهُ",
        "answer": "its interior",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "bāṭinuhu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدُ",
        "answer": "afterwards",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "baʿdu",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْتِغَاءَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ib'tighāa",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنِ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ib'ni",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَابٌ",
        "answer": "a gate",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "bābun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيَّنَّا",
        "answer": "We have made clear",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "bayyannā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "among you",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "baynakum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "bayyinātin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعُوهُ",
        "answer": "followed him",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿūhu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flowing",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He has made you",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "jaʿalakum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We placed",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We placed",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "and He will make",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "wayajʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٌ",
        "answer": "gardens",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "jannātun",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "and a Garden",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "wajannatin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَدِيدَ",
        "answer": "[the] iron",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ḥadīda",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "goodly",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "goodly",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the best",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُطَامًا",
        "answer": "debris",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥuṭāman",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "(with) right",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمِيدُ",
        "answer": "the Praiseworthy",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamīdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "He gives life",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "gives life",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the life",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "khabīrun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "comes forth",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yakhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُخْرِجَكُمْ",
        "answer": "that He may bring you out",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "liyukh'rijakum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْشَعَ",
        "answer": "become humble",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "takhshaʿa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "abiding forever",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَخْلَفِينَ",
        "answer": "trustees",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "mus'takhlafīna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْتَالٍ",
        "answer": "self-deluded",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mukh'tālin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَرَجَةً",
        "answer": "(in) degree",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "darajatan",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "calls you",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "yadʿūkum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتِهِمَا",
        "answer": "their offspring",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatihimā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "at (the) remembrance (of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "lidhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأْفَةً",
        "answer": "compassion",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "rafatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَرَءُوفٌ",
        "answer": "(is the) Most Kind",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "laraūfun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَى",
        "answer": "you will see",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَاهُ",
        "answer": "and you see it",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "fatarāhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "in your Lord",
        "pcklId": "861",
        "tlit": "birabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "862",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "863",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَبَّصْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you awaited",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "watarabbaṣtum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُ",
        "answer": "will be returned",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْجِعُوا",
        "answer": "Go back",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ir'jiʿū",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَةُ",
        "answer": "(is) mercy",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmatu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(the) Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "while the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "wal-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُسُلِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messengers",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "warusulihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُسُلِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messengers",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "warusulihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلَنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messengers",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "rusulanā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرُسُلَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messengers",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "warusulahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُسُلِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Messengers",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "birusulinā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "in His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "birasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانٌ",
        "answer": "and Pleasure",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِضْوَانِ",
        "answer": "(the) pleasure",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "riḍ'wāni",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَعَوْهَا",
        "answer": "they observed it",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "raʿawhā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِعَايَتِهَا",
        "answer": "observance",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "riʿāyatihā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَهْبَانِيَّةً",
        "answer": "But monasticism",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "warahbāniyyatan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْتَبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you doubted",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'tabtum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزِينَةٌ",
        "answer": "and adornment",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wazīnatun",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَّحَ",
        "answer": "Glorifies",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "sabbaḥa",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَابِقُوا",
        "answer": "Race",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "sābiqū",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِتَّةِ",
        "answer": "six",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sittati",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "running",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heaven",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسُورٍ",
        "answer": "a wall",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bisūrin",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "He rose",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوِي",
        "answer": "are equal",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yastawī",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٌ",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "shadīdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٌ",
        "answer": "mighty",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "shadīdun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشُّهَدَاءُ",
        "answer": "and the martyrs",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "wal-shuhadāu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "491",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "492",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "493",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّدُورِ",
        "answer": "of what is in the breasts",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّدِّيقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the truthful",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-ṣidīqūna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُصَّدِّقَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the women who give charity",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "wal-muṣadiqāti",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُصَّدِّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the men who give charity",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "l-muṣadiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصْفَرًّا",
        "answer": "turning yellow",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "muṣ'farran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَابَ",
        "answer": "strikes",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "aṣāba",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصِيبَةٍ",
        "answer": "disaster",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "muṣībatin",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "the destination",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضُرِبَ",
        "answer": "Then will be put up",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "faḍuriba",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُضَاعِفَهُ",
        "answer": "so He will multiply it",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fayuḍāʿifahu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضَاعَفُ",
        "answer": "it will be multiplied",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yuḍāʿafu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَالَ",
        "answer": "(and) was prolonged",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faṭāla",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالظَّاهِرُ",
        "answer": "and the Apparent",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wal-ẓāhiru",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَاهِرُهُ",
        "answer": "but its exterior",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "waẓāhiruhu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبْدِهِ",
        "answer": "His slave",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "ʿabdihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَبَ",
        "answer": "pleases",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aʿjaba",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُعِدَّتْ",
        "answer": "prepared",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "uʿiddat",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرُجُ",
        "answer": "ascends",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaʿruju",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "the Throne",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرْضُهَا",
        "answer": "its width",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ʿarḍuhā",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَعَرْضِ",
        "answer": "(is) like (the) width",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "kaʿarḍi",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزٌ",
        "answer": "All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْظَمُ",
        "answer": "(are) greater",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aʿẓamu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Great",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Great",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "understand",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "Know",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "Know",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "iʿ'lamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "and so that Allah may make evident",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "waliyaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "may know",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "yaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "758",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "813",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(are) with",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَرَّتْكُمُ",
        "answer": "and deceived you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wagharratkumu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَرَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "And deceived you",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wagharrakum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغُرُورِ",
        "answer": "(of) delusion",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ghurūri",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَرُورُ",
        "answer": "the deceiver",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-gharūru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "and He will forgive",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wayaghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَغْفِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "and forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "wamaghfiratun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْفِرَةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "maghfiratin",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَنِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) Free of need",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-ghaniyu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "unseen",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "bil-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْثٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a rain",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ghaythin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَتْحِ",
        "answer": "the victory",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-fatḥi",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "led to temptation",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fatantum",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخُورٍ",
        "answer": "boaster",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fakhūrin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَفَاخُرٌ",
        "answer": "and boasting",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "watafākhurun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِدْيَةٌ",
        "answer": "any ransom",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fid'yatun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْرَحُوا",
        "answer": "exult",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "tafraḥū",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobediently",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) defiantly disobediently",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "fāsiqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Bounty",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "faḍlu",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَضْلِ",
        "answer": "(is) the Possessor of Bounty",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-faḍli",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) Bounty",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "faḍli",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَضْلَ",
        "answer": "the Bounty",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-faḍla",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَضْلِ",
        "answer": "(is) the Possessor of Bounty",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-faḍli",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has escaped you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fātakum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "the success",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقْتَبِسْ",
        "answer": "we may acquire",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naqtabis",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِبَلِهِ",
        "answer": "facing towards [it]",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "qibalihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاتَلَ",
        "answer": "and fought",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "waqātala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاتَلُوا",
        "answer": "and fought",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "waqātalū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْدِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they have power",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yaqdirūna",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْرِضُ",
        "answer": "will loan",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuq'riḍu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْرَضُوا",
        "answer": "and who lend",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-aqraḍū",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْضًا",
        "answer": "a loan",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "qarḍan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْضًا",
        "answer": "a loan",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "qarḍan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقِسْطِ",
        "answer": "justice",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "bil-qis'ṭi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَسَتْ",
        "answer": "so hardened",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "faqasat",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَفَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "qaffaynā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَفَّيْنَا",
        "answer": "and We followed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waqaffaynā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِ",
        "answer": "(the) hearts",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "qulūbi",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "1521",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "It will be said",
        "pcklId": "1522",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "1523",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَقُومَ",
        "answer": "that may establish",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "liyaqūma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Strong",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "qawiyyun",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "kabīrun",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "We prescribed it",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "katabnāhā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "a Register",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "kitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "and the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "wal-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَثِيرٌ",
        "answer": "and many",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "wakathīrun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَثِيرٌ",
        "answer": "but most",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "wakathīrun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَثِيرٌ",
        "answer": "but most",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "wakathīrun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَكَاثُرٌ",
        "answer": "and competition in increase",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "watakāthurun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "and deny",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "wakadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٌ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "karīmun",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٌ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "karīmun",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارَ",
        "answer": "the tillers",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "l-kufāra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِفْلَيْنِ",
        "answer": "double portion",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "kif'layni",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "(is) of every",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "But to all",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "wakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1257",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1258",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكُنْ",
        "answer": "we",
        "pcklId": "1259",
        "tlit": "nakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "they become",
        "pcklId": "1260",
        "tlit": "yakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "becomes",
        "pcklId": "1261",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعِبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) play",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "laʿibun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْتَمِسُوا",
        "answer": "and seek",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fal-tamisū",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَهْوٌ",
        "answer": "and amusement",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "walahwun",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعُ",
        "answer": "(the) enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "matāʿu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "like (the) example",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْشُونَ",
        "answer": "you will walk",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tamshūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمَانِيُّ",
        "answer": "the wishful thinking",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-amāniyu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُمِيتُ",
        "answer": "and causes death",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wayumītu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتِهَا",
        "answer": "its death",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "mawtihā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْوَالِ",
        "answer": "the wealth",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-amwāli",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّبُوَّةَ",
        "answer": "Prophethood",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-nubuwata",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَاتُهُ",
        "answer": "its growth",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "nabātuhu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَادُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "They will call them",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yunādūnahum",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْزِلُ",
        "answer": "descends",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yanzilu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَلَ",
        "answer": "has come down",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "nazala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلُ",
        "answer": "sends down",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "yunazzilu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We sent down",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "wa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We sent down",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "wa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُهُ",
        "answer": "helps Him",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yanṣuruhu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرُونَا",
        "answer": "Wait for us",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "unẓurūnā",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "anfusakum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "yourselves",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَنَافِعُ",
        "answer": "and benefits",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wamanāfiʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "and spend",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wa-anfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفَقُوا",
        "answer": "and spend",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wa-anfaqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "you spend",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "tunfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفَقَ",
        "answer": "spent",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "anfaqa",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفَقُوا",
        "answer": "spent",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "anfaqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنَافِقَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the hypocrite women",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "wal-munāfiqātu",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقُونَ",
        "answer": "the hypocrite men",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-munāfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "l-nāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّورِ",
        "answer": "the light",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "l-nūri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their light",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "nūruhum",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your light",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "nūrikum",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورًا",
        "answer": "light",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "nūran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُورُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their light",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "wanūruhum",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورًا",
        "answer": "a light",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "nūran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "(on) the people",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the people",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْتَدٍ",
        "answer": "(is) a guided one",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "muh'tadin",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهِيجُ",
        "answer": "it dries",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yahīju",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your covenant",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "mīthāqakum",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيرَاثُ",
        "answer": "(is the) heritage",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "mīrāthu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "behind you",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "warāakum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمِيزَانَ",
        "answer": "and the Balance",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wal-mīzāna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلِجُ",
        "answer": "penetrates",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaliju",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُولِجُ",
        "answer": "He merges",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yūliju",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُولِجُ",
        "answer": "and He merges",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wayūliju",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَوْلَادِ",
        "answer": "and the children",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "wal-awlādi",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yatawalla",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْلَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "your protector",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "mawlākum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَدِ",
        "answer": "(is) in Allah s Hand",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "biyadi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) easy",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yasīrun",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِأَيْمَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and on their right",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wabi-aymānihim",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "periods",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(On the) Day",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "this Day ",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(On the) Day",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "So today",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "fal-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "57",
        "ayah": "15"
    }
]; 
export default words;